{
    "subject": "resource/Homonotichthys",
    "predicate": "ontology/class",
    "object": "resource/Actinopterygii",
    "human_readable": "Homonotichthys is classified under Actinopterygii.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6554551720619202,
            "question": "Give an example of a fish classified under Actinopterygii."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5761093497276306,
            "question": "What characteristics define Actinopterygii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5623325109481812,
            "question": "What class does Homonotichthys belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5599948167800903,
            "question": "To which group of fish does Actinopterygii belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.539905846118927,
            "question": "How does Actinopterygii differ from other fish classifications?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5002649426460266,
            "question": "What is the common name for Homonotichthys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4799383282661438,
            "question": "Can you describe the evolutionary history of Actinopterygii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4565621018409729,
            "question": "Are there any other types of fish besides Actinopterygii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42141661047935486,
            "question": "Where might you find a Homonotichthys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38394883275032043,
            "question": "What are some unique features of Homonotichthys?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Homonotichthys is classified under Actinopterygii.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4261_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might you find a Homonotichthys?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4261_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other types of fish besides Actinopterygii?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4261_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the evolutionary history of Actinopterygii?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4261_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4261_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4261_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4261_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4261_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4261_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4261_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4261_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4261_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4261_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4261_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple \"Homonotichthys is classified under Actinopterygii\":\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to the documents, Homonotichthys (specifically its similar close relative Psarolepis) are eugnathostomes but they remember their placoderm-grade origins. However, there is no mention of Homonotichthys being classified under Actinopterygii in the provided context information.\n\nHowever, I have found a mention of Dialipina markae which is described as a basal actinopterygian based on its possession of ganoid scales. Clement et al., 2018, however, recover it as a stem osteichthyan."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that Homonotichthys is classified under Actinopterygii, as it discusses Actinopterygii extensively and describes its characteristics and subcategories."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Homonotichthys being classified under Actinopterygii, and the provided context only discusses the classification of Osteichthyes into two subclasses (Sarcopterygii and Actinopterygii) and the further subdivision of Actinopterygii into several classes and infraclasses.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}